* [VM Images](# "Virtual Machines (VirtualBox & VMware) Images")

* [VM Images](# "Virtual Machines (VirtualBox & VMware) Images")

Privacy Policy
==============

Privacy Policy
--------------

[Umair](https://www.osboxes.org/author/umair-riaz/ "Posts by Umair")2017-12-30T23:28:47+02:00

**Legal**
---------

We only offer those operating system images that are distributed under an open-source license. Due to some [blobs](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Binary_blob "Binacy Blob Wiki") stuff, we refer to the “[OSI open source](http://www.opensource.org/docs/osd)” license. We do not include any **free or non-free package/any kind of file/stuff** in images and referring you to operating systems websites to know their licensing terms (documentation/terms & conditions/license of each operating system is available on their websites).

On our site we have used trademarks and logos of VirtualBox™, VMware™, and other corporations (like Ubuntu, Fedora, Opensuse, and so on), all these names and logos are registered trademarks of their respective corporations. We do not intend to infringe any product/service.

**Privacy Policy**
------------------

**Virtual images notes:**

We **_do not_** install any kind of package in any distribution that is available here or _**do not**_ add any kind of file/script or _**do not**_ perform update or _**do not**_ configure anything in the Operating System, virtual images for VirtualBox and VMware are only available with default options. We believe that user should get a clean install image. From our site you get fresh image with default options (we do not modify anything within the image), just like you install fresh OS, after getting image you can make it your own. **Our images are 100% free from malware/spyware/bloatware/adware and so**. Feel free to **audit** any image you download from **here**, after that also **send audit report** to us(we may feature your report).

**Information we collect:**

Privacy of your personal information is very important to us. We **never** disclose any of your information to third-party or any other person, when you visit our site. Here are some details which information our site collect.

We collect data contained from our site log files, the information in the log files include your ISP (internet service provider) info, the web browser you are using, your IP (internet protocol) address, and the time duration you’ve visited our site and which pages you’ve explored.

We’re not responsible for any external linked sites. We recommend you to read privacy policy before disclosing any personal information to them.

**Cookies:**

Cookies are part of every website now a days, cookies used to store information for advertisement, analytics, and social interaction. We are using Google Analytics; Adsense for advertisements; Facebook, Google Plus, and Twitter for social interaction; and Disqus service as commenting system.

You may opt-out of the use of DART cookie by visiting [here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

_Your browser can turn-off cookies for our site or selectively third-party cookies or disable cookies within settings_

However, this step will affect your browser interaction with our website as well as other websites.

**Commenting Policy:**

Visitor should not abuse anyone or defame any product on our site. We may delete your comment, if found offended. Be nice, polite, respective and so on. 🙂

### Share this post

#### **Support This Project**

* * *

* * *

**Credentials for images:**  
username: osboxes  
password: osboxes.org  
Root account password: osboxes.org

### Recent Posts

##### [Parrot Security OS 6.1 Images Released for VirtualBox and VMware](https://www.osboxes.org/parrot-security-os-6-1-images-released-for-virtualbox-and-vmware/)

08-06-2024

##### [Linux Lite 7.0 Virtual Machine Images Available for VirtualBox and VMware](https://www.osboxes.org/linux-lite-7-0-virtual-machine-images-available-for-virtualbox-and-vmware/)

06-06-2024

##### [Fedora 40 and Server VM Images Available for VirtualBox and VMware](https://www.osboxes.org/fedora-40-and-server-vm-images-available-for-virtualbox-and-vmware/)

05-06-2024

##### [Ubuntu 24.04 and Ubuntu Server 24.04 Images for VirtualBox and VMware](https://www.osboxes.org/ubuntu-24-04-and-ubuntu-server-24-04-images-for-virtualbox-and-vmware/)

04-06-2024

##### [Parrot Security OS 6.0 Images Released for VirtualBox and VMware](https://www.osboxes.org/parrot-security-os-6-0-images-released-for-virtualbox-and-vmware/)

18-03-2024

##### [Kali Linux 2024.1 VM Images Available for VirtualBox and VMware](https://www.osboxes.org/kali-linux-2024-1-vm-images-available-for-virtualbox-and-vmware/)

18-03-2024

Get in Touch!

### Follow us

### Links

Tutorials for:  

### Acknowledgements

The terms & logos we've used **VirtualBox™**, **VMware™** and **others** are registered trademarks for their respective corporations, and used on this site for reference proposes only. Infringing behavior isn't intended.

Our site is using cookies, by visiting our site you are agree to use of cookies. Read our [privacy policy](https://www.osboxes.org/privacy-policy/).

OSBoxes ©. All Rights Reserved.

We use cookies on our website to give you the most relevant experience by remembering your preferences and repeat visits. By clicking “Accept All”, you consent to the use of ALL the cookies. However, you may visit "Cookie Settings" to provide a controlled consent.

Cookie SettingsAccept All

Manage consent

Close

#### Privacy Overview

This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.

Necessary

 Necessary

Always Enabled

Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.

Non-necessary

 Non-necessary

Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.

SAVE & ACCEPT

* **Donate This Project**
    -----------------------
    
    **You can keep this project alive by donation or disable your “Adblocker” for this website. Thank You!**

Do not show for a Month
